[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "Do you ever sit here, just the three of you sometimes, and think, how did we get here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ashton", "Birmingham"]}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "I mean, I just wonder whether sometimes you have that moment where you just think how did this happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "You know, I had the occasion to go back to the house I grew up in Ashton, Birmingham a few months ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozzy"]}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Sharon, how did you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I was kind of one up from Ozzy because we had inside bathrooms in our house.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "If you had your time again, would you choose to be in that MTV show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Absolutely, yes, because -- I mean, I wouldn't be here talking to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "If you had the choice now to make that series or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "It's a very difficult question for me to answer because I did -- it became huger than I ever expected it to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "And what do you think of that, coming from Britain and going back there and seeing it's so much more prevalent now, given what it did to you and your life and the impact on your family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, I'm lucky.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Do you feel lucky that none of your kids ended up like Amy Winehouse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Lucky is not the word.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy Winehouse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozzy"]}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I think she said -- she's including you as one of the children, Ozzy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", ":", "NNP", ":", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "How do they think their bodies can continue doing this, and doing this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", ",", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "But then at the same time, it has nothing to do with the size, the age, the width, (INAUDIBLE), it's to do with the look.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "People you've known?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "A lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "What do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "When you watched her talking about that, Ozzy, what did you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "It's only now, it's only after the fact, my folks never said, you know, I didn't think about anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozzy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "I mean, that's an extraordinary moment to reach, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "I don't know, because I can't remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Well, in a funny way, in the movie -- in the movie, it was a bit surreal watching that because, Sharon was able to kind of deal with it in a relatively calm way when in fact it must have been at the time just grotesque, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "It was -- it was pretty damn scary because, you know, you're in a house, no neighbors each side, your kids are asleep.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What was the answer when you ask yourself that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Oh, God, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozzy"]}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "JJR", ":", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "How would you imagine that you're a shrinking violet in any relationship, Sharon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "No, as harder -- as hard as Ozzy would hit me, I would clobber him back.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sharon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 227, "question": "What do you feel when you hear that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Honestly, it's just kind of --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Never in front of the kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "You never hit a girl.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "So what about you (EXPLETIVE DELETED) hitting us then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Yes, that's exactly right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "But do you feel, Ozzy, you're a completely different human being now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozzy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "And to put the flipside on it, was it for a long time great fun being Ozzy Osbourne?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "It was great fun until it wasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Enough of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Sharon, would you go along with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Had you pissed on me as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "And Jack just cracked up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "You don't agree, Ozzy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozzy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "It wasn't Jack reacting to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Maybe was.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Jack, do you remember the incident your mom is talking about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "What have you got against bats?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I did some have crazy stuff when I was out there, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Am I misreading the tea leaves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "My mom's a very strong-willed woman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Is that understood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Without a doubt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Even now, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "The whole thing was --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Dad likes to slam things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Ozzy, would you say you have anger management issues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "What was that like, do you think, in reality for the family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "It was the strangest thing because we were all on such a big high from the show being such a success.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Why are we living our lives in this crazy soap opera when it's so serious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "They were very respectful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Did you think Ozzy could have coped if you had died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Jack, what was it like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "No one really told me the severity of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What were you thinking, Ozzy, as you were lying in hospital?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I wanted to get out.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozzy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Never boring, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "How did he feel about the way you were enjoying all that fame?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "On his death bed, this is what he -- on his death bed, he said to me -- the only thing I have to say to you -- he thought all drugs were speed or sleeping pills.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Do you think he would have been very proud of you, of what you've now done with your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I know he would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "I mean, he was a nice guy in his own way, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Sharon, you had very much more complicated relationship with your father.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "When that happened, what was your real emotion when you realized he was no longer going to be any part of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I got the most amazing gifts from my father, the gift of music.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Horrified?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I was pissed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I'd been drinking big time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What did you think when you heard it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozzy"]}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBD", ",", "IN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "What did I think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "All I could think of was, because as usual, as soon as Ozzy and I get down to a table, we're throwing in the food, and he had a big pat of butter on his crotch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Do you care much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", ":", "NNP", ":", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "I don't understand it, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "It is an almost impossible job these days because the news cycle is so relentless, that people just get bored with the president very quickly, (INAUDIBLE), how it's a better story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "What do you think, Sharon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Do you think President Obama is still too young?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I think he's an incredible man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "What do you think of America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I just like it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Did you ever imagine, Jack, your father would become a sort of medical advisory board?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "It wouldn't surprise me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "How did it keep going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "I haven't got a clue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Do you feel like all the torment has been worth it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon", "Sharon"]}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "We're so lucky, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "You know, I was meant to be with Sharon and Sharon was meant to be with me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Jack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Where did we find little Jack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Jack is a lone voice of sanity.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "I'm excited.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Ozzy, how are you feeling about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "I'm in shock.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Good shock?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "I think it is fabulous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "You are not a grandma, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]